<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Online Election</string>
    <string name="readme">
        Please read these Terms of Service carefully before accessing or using the service.
        By registering for or using the service in any manner, your are expected to run the on-line election
        service by voting the parties you like to vote.
        Certain of the service may be subject to additional terms and conditions specified by Election runner from time to time.
        Election runner reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to modify or replace any terms od service.
        If you are using organization Emails for registrations, your vote will be declined.
        You are solely responsible for the activity that occurs on your Account.
        We shall not be liable to you or to any third-party for any modification, suspension or discontinuance of the Service.
        By accessing or using any part of the app, you agree to be bound by these Terms of Service.
        If you do not agree to all the terms and conditions of this agreement, then you may not access the app or use any services.
        If these Terms of Service are considered an offer, acceptance is expressly limited to these Terms of service.
        These Terms of service apply to all users of the service.
    </string>
    <string name="abotus"> This app is developed to make a platform for online election.
                          In this project included Firebase, Firebasedata, and Firestore.
        Developed By: Yeshak Mesfin.
        Email: Isaacmesfin@gmail.com
        Github: IsaacMesfin69

    </string>
    <string name="term">Read the Following Terms!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">Home</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="open">Open</string>

</resources>